Ismail gamal Mahmoud

(+02)01011494727/ (+02)01114951082 / <u>ismailgamal1000@gmail.com</u>

Senior Land Surveyor

Objective

Experienced land surveyor with +10 years of experience, with master knowledge of land surveying techniques, methods, rules and regulations. Three years of experience as an auditor, providing a unique perspective and skill set to the role. Can double the number of surveys completed every month with accuracy, timeliness and unparalleled precision.

Education

• Degree in surveying.

The institute of surveying and irrigation, Asyut, Grad: B+

YEARS 9/1/2012 to 6/1/2014

Experience

ASHADA, EGYPT

Job Title : Senior Land Surveyor Project : Park Lane , New Capital

Owner: Al-Attal Group Holding Consultant: DMA 32 Building

responsible

- Verifying data and calculations.
- Recording results of surveys.
- Calculating the measurements of sites.
- Writing descriptions of property boundaries.
- Researching legal documents, survey records, and land titles to clarify information about property boundaries.
- -Involved in planning and conducting ground surveys designed to establish baselines, elevations, and other geodetic measurements.
- Wrote descriptions of property boundary surveys for use in deeds, leases, or other legal documents.
- Searched legal records, survey records, and land titles in order to obtain information about property boundaries in areas to be surveyed.
- Coordinated findings with the work of engineering and architectural personnel, clients, and others concerned with projects.
- Preparing quantities Cut and Fill Grading

El Shames Contractor Roads, EGYPT

Job Title : Land Surveyor

Project : Helwan Central Corniche Street

: Road Bellbes (gesr suze): Road 9th street Moqatm

responsible

- Verifying data and calculations.
- Recording results of surveys.
- Calculating the measurements of sites.
- Writing descriptions of property boundaries.
- Researching legal documents, survey records, and land titles to clarify information about property boundaries.
- -Involved in planning and conducting ground surveys designed to establish baselines, elevations, and other geodetic measurements.

DMC Curve Dar Al Mimar, EGYPT

Date 2015 TO 2018

Date 2018 TO 2022

Job Title : Land Surveyor

Project: I city 5th settlement Mountain View

responsible

- Verifying data and calculations.
- Recording results of surveys.
- Calculating the measurements of sites.
- Writing descriptions of property boundaries.
- Researching legal documents, survey records, and land titles to clarify information about property boundaries.
- -Involved in planning and conducting ground surveys designed to establish baselines, elevations, and other geodetic measurements.

Skills

- Interpersonal Skills
- Accuracy
- Communication Skills
- Detail-oriented
- Multitasking

Technical Skills

Autodesk (CAD)

Autodesk (Civil 3D)

Geographic information systems (GIS)

Global Mapper

Sokia Link , Pro link

Microsoft office

Langue

Arabic Mother tongue

English .B1

Personal Information

Birth data: 1st March 1994

Military service: Completed

Gender : Male

marital status: Married